<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Monofilaments, Fishing Lines, Pet Lines, Sewing Threads, Lawn Trimmer on TECHMONFIL</title>
    <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Monofilaments, Fishing Lines, Pet Lines, Sewing Threads, Lawn Trimmer on TECHMONFIL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://techmonfil.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PET-POLYESTER</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pet-polyester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pet-polyester/</guid>
      <description>PET monofilament is primarily used for the purposes of textile market.
The main fields of application are the production of curtain tapes, conveyor belts, tensile and binding belts, zips for clothing industry and filters for the paper industry.
Due to the nature of the raw material (its high melting point) and the formulation procedure it is subjected to, this type of monofilament presents great resistance against high temperatures and abrasion. This characteristic is easily recognised by the amount of resistance this monofilament presents against deformability and by its good reaction to chemical agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STRING TRIMMER</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/technical_applications/string-trimmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/technical_applications/string-trimmer/</guid>
      <description>High-quality monofilament line suitable for string trimmers.
 Excellent abrasion resistance and durability. Distinctive colours to ensure high visibility while running the trimmer. Wide variety in colours, shapes and diameters.  Produced in:
 Diameters: 1.30 - 4.00 mm Shapes: Square &amp;amp; Round  String trimer shapes.  Packaging:
 Donut of 25 - 100m Pre-cut 30 cm lines, ready to use Spools 2 - 3 Kg Kilometer hanks 3 - 4 Kg  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraline</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/terraline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/terraline/</guid>
      <description>Terraline is a higly tensile strength fishing line that our company exclusively produces. Its knot strength can reach even twice the tensile strength of normal fishing lines. Due to its high knot strength, its flexibility, its resistence to spiralling, Terraline can definitely meet the needs of every amateur fisherman.
Terraline is available in a broad range of packages and its quality is considered one of the best in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinylon</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/trinylon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/trinylon/</guid>
      <description>Being continually produced for over 30 years now, Trinylon represents the classic quality of Techmonfil monofilaments, whose balanced qualities can equally serve both professional and amateur users&amp;rsquo; needs.
Its high transparency, flexibility and satisfying tensile strength guarantee a highly quality product that can be purchased at reasonable prices. These characteristics have established Trinylon as the best selling fishing line in Greece.
Packings:
 Hanks of 1 Km. Spools with a net weight of 1, 2 or 3 Kg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nautilon</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/nautilon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/nautilon/</guid>
      <description>The use of highly developed co-polymers combined with the advanced technology Techmonfil developed especially for the production of a high tensile strength fishing line. Its knot strength can reach even twice the tensile strength of normal fishing lines.
Packings:
 Hanks of 1 Km. Spools with a net weight of 2 or 3 Kg. Spools of 100, 300 and 500 m (TERRALINE)  Availiable diameters: 0.20 - 1.57 mm.
Availiable colours: White and grey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nautilon</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/nautilon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/nautilon/</guid>
      <description>The use of highly developed co-polymers combined with the advanced technology Techmonfil developed especially for the production of a high tensile strength fishing line. Its knot strength can reach even twice the tensile strength of normal fishing lines.
Packings:
 Hanks of one Km. Spools with a net weight of two or three Kg. Spools of 100 - 300 - 500 m (TERRALINE)  Diameters: 0,20 - 1,57 mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PA-POLYAMIDE</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pa-polyamide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pa-polyamide/</guid>
      <description>This monofilament is purposed to be used as a sewing thread. Its basic raw material is polyamide.
In order to serve the needs of the textile industry we have developed a PA monofilament line which is transparent and doesn’t shrink when exposed to high temperatures. It also demonstrates high tensile strength, abrasion and and a great diameter uniformity.
It can be used to sew any type of garment either for industrial or amateur purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profile</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/profile/</guid>
      <description>The branch of Techmonfil in Athens(at 75 Kefallinias Str., Moschato), has been the place of production of monofilament lines since 1972.
Part of the initial equipment came under the today&amp;rsquo;s owners ownership in 1988, when a change of proprietorship of the 1972-founded company occurred. That point of time initiated the modernization of the company and the struggling effort for the production of the most up-to-date monofilament products. In the following 15 years of its function, the &amp;ldquo;KAPSILIS-TRIANTIS&amp;rdquo; company which was later on renamed as &amp;ldquo;TECHMONFIL-K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nautilon Multicolour</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/nautilon_multicolour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/nautilon_multicolour/</guid>
      <description>Techmonfil, the greek company which produces monofilaments that are guaranteed for their quality and comply with the highest international standarts, presents an alternative of the already successful Nautilon fishing line. A class on its own, Nautilon multicolour fishing line offers you the choice to use of alternative colours so that you discover the most appropriate colour for the method and the place you are fishing.
Its characteristics are balanced flexibility, no memory and excellent knot strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PE-PΟLYETHYLENE</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pe-polyethylene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pe-polyethylene/</guid>
      <description>Raw Material: High Density Polyethylene (HDPE).
Fields of application: Production of mosquito nets, nets for the food industry, nets for the agricultural industry such as nets for the collection of olives, tow ropes, tapes for the furniture industry, special nets for sports camps. PE can also be used as a contributory factor in certain paper or plastic products.
Colours: Light green, dark green, red, white and any other colour by order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinylon</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/trinylon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/trinylon/</guid>
      <description>Η γνωστή πετονιά TRINYLON σε καρούλια πολλών χιλιομέτρων, προσφέρεται για μία ευρεία γκάμα χρήσεων στους τομείς της αλιείας και της κλωστοϋφαντουργίας. Προσφέρεται είτε μαλακωμένη είτε αμαλάκωτη σε διάφορες συσκευασίες καρουλιών (ανάλογα με την διάμετρο της καρουλοποιημένης μισινέζας).
Η υψηλή της διαφάνεια, η ευκαμψία και η ικανοποιητική της αντοχή πλαισιώνονται από μία αρκετά συμφέρουσα σχέση τιμής-ποιότητας.
Διατίθεται σε διαμέτρους: 0,25 - 2,50 mm.
Και σε χρώματα: Λευκό, θαλασσί, πράσινο, κίτρινο και κόκκινο.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbofil</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/carbofil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/carbofil/</guid>
      <description>A fishing line of 100% Fluorocarbon with a diffraction index similar to water. Thanks to its material it is invisible and sinkable inside the water.
Availible packages:
 Spools from 100 to 500m. Hanks from 300 to 1000m. Diameters from 0.10 mm to 1.20 mm.  Diameter Tensile Strength  Ø (mm) Kg    0.10 0.8   0.12  1.1   0.14 1.8   0.18 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexonyl</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/flexonyl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/flexonyl/</guid>
      <description>The use of advanced raw material combined with the unique production techniques developed by Techmonfil for the production of a particularly flexible fishing line resulted in the creation of Flexonyl. Despite its high flexibility Flexonyl sustains its high tensial strength. Its flexibility remains intact even after many plunges in the water.
Packings: Hanks of 1 Km.
Available diameters: 0.60 - 2.50 mm.
Available colours: White, Green, Navy blue, Yellow.
Hanks of 1 Km.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PP-POLYPROPELENE</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pp-polypropylene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pp-polypropylene/</guid>
      <description>Raw material: Polypropylene
Fields of application: Curtain tapes, filters and more.
Resistant to acids and other chemical derivatives.
Colours: Transparent, white and any other colour by order.
Diameters: 0.18 - 0.35 mm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quality Guarantee</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/quality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/quality/</guid>
      <description>At Techmonfil, we are dedicated to quality and constant improvement of our products and we work hard to meet the needs even of the most demanding customer.
To ensure superior performance of our monofilament lines we perform constant quality tests, which include:
 Determination of ultimate tensile strength. Measurement of elongation until breakage. Measurement of elongation in predetermined tension. Determination of dtex. (Mass of filament lengthening 10,000 m) Shrinking percentage (after immersion in hot water).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbonyl</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/carbonyl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/carbonyl/</guid>
      <description>This fishing line is coated with fluorocarbon. Its main benefits are that it does not absorb water and its performance is not reduced inside the water.
The nylon that it contains, ensures excellent tensile strength and resistance that surpass those of pure fluorocarbon.
Available packages:
 Spools from 100 to 300m. Hanks from 300 to 1000m.  100 m spool.  Round spool in blister package.  Package of hanks 300 - 1000 m.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact us</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/contact/</guid>
      <description> TECHMONFIL K. TRIANTIS &amp; Co. P.C. THESI PALIO CHORIO 20003 AGIOI THEODOROI KORINTHIAS TEL.: 27410-49942 FAX: 27410-49943 info@techmonfil.gr  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecoline</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/ecoline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/ecoline/</guid>
      <description>Ecoline is the economical quality of Techmonfil fishing lines. Despite its low price, it demonstrates satisfactory technical characteristics. The increased productivity of Techmonfil since the company&amp;rsquo;s relocation in the new premises in Ag. Theodoroi Korinthias allows for products of good quality, but also inexpensive.
Packings: Hanks of 1 Km.
Hanks of 1 Km.   Diameter Tensile Strength  Ø (mm) Kg    0.50 13.5   0.60 18.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>