<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hanks on TECHMONFIL</title>
    <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hanks on TECHMONFIL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinylon</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/trinylon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/trinylon/</guid>
      <description>Being continually produced for over 30 years now, Trinylon represents the classic quality of Techmonfil monofilaments, whose balanced qualities can equally serve both professional and amateur users&amp;rsquo; needs.
Its high transparency, flexibility and satisfying tensile strength guarantee a highly quality product that can be purchased at reasonable prices. These characteristics have established Trinylon as the best selling fishing line in Greece.
Packings:
 Hanks of 1 Km. Spools with a net weight of 1, 2 or 3 Kg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nautilon</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/nautilon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/nautilon/</guid>
      <description>The use of highly developed co-polymers combined with the advanced technology Techmonfil developed especially for the production of a high tensile strength fishing line. Its knot strength can reach even twice the tensile strength of normal fishing lines.
Packings:
 Hanks of 1 Km. Spools with a net weight of 2 or 3 Kg. Spools of 100, 300 and 500 m (TERRALINE)  Availiable diameters: 0.20 - 1.57 mm.
Availiable colours: White and grey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nautilon Multicolour</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/nautilon_multicolour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/nautilon_multicolour/</guid>
      <description>Techmonfil, the greek company which produces monofilaments that are guaranteed for their quality and comply with the highest international standarts, presents an alternative of the already successful Nautilon fishing line. A class on its own, Nautilon multicolour fishing line offers you the choice to use of alternative colours so that you discover the most appropriate colour for the method and the place you are fishing.
Its characteristics are balanced flexibility, no memory and excellent knot strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexonyl</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/flexonyl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/flexonyl/</guid>
      <description>The use of advanced raw material combined with the unique production techniques developed by Techmonfil for the production of a particularly flexible fishing line resulted in the creation of Flexonyl. Despite its high flexibility Flexonyl sustains its high tensial strength. Its flexibility remains intact even after many plunges in the water.
Packings: Hanks of 1 Km.
Available diameters: 0.60 - 2.50 mm.
Available colours: White, Green, Navy blue, Yellow.
Hanks of 1 Km.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecoline</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/ecoline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/hanks/ecoline/</guid>
      <description>Ecoline is the economical quality of Techmonfil fishing lines. Despite its low price, it demonstrates satisfactory technical characteristics. The increased productivity of Techmonfil since the company&amp;rsquo;s relocation in the new premises in Ag. Theodoroi Korinthias allows for products of good quality, but also inexpensive.
Packings: Hanks of 1 Km.
Hanks of 1 Km.   Diameter Tensile Strength  Ø (mm) Kg    0.50 13.5   0.60 18.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>