<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spools on TECHMONFIL</title>
    <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spools on TECHMONFIL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraline</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/terraline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/terraline/</guid>
      <description>Terraline is a higly tensile strength fishing line that our company exclusively produces. Its knot strength can reach even twice the tensile strength of normal fishing lines. Due to its high knot strength, its flexibility, its resistence to spiralling, Terraline can definitely meet the needs of every amateur fisherman.
Terraline is available in a broad range of packages and its quality is considered one of the best in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nautilon</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/nautilon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/nautilon/</guid>
      <description>The use of highly developed co-polymers combined with the advanced technology Techmonfil developed especially for the production of a high tensile strength fishing line. Its knot strength can reach even twice the tensile strength of normal fishing lines.
Packings:
 Hanks of one Km. Spools with a net weight of two or three Kg. Spools of 100 - 300 - 500 m (TERRALINE)  Diameters: 0,20 - 1,57 mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trinylon</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/trinylon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/trinylon/</guid>
      <description>Η γνωστή πετονιά TRINYLON σε καρούλια πολλών χιλιομέτρων, προσφέρεται για μία ευρεία γκάμα χρήσεων στους τομείς της αλιείας και της κλωστοϋφαντουργίας. Προσφέρεται είτε μαλακωμένη είτε αμαλάκωτη σε διάφορες συσκευασίες καρουλιών (ανάλογα με την διάμετρο της καρουλοποιημένης μισινέζας).
Η υψηλή της διαφάνεια, η ευκαμψία και η ικανοποιητική της αντοχή πλαισιώνονται από μία αρκετά συμφέρουσα σχέση τιμής-ποιότητας.
Διατίθεται σε διαμέτρους: 0,25 - 2,50 mm.
Και σε χρώματα: Λευκό, θαλασσί, πράσινο, κίτρινο και κόκκινο.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbofil</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/carbofil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/carbofil/</guid>
      <description>A fishing line of 100% Fluorocarbon with a diffraction index similar to water. Thanks to its material it is invisible and sinkable inside the water.
Availible packages:
 Spools from 100 to 500m. Hanks from 300 to 1000m. Diameters from 0.10 mm to 1.20 mm.  Diameter Tensile Strength  Ø (mm) Kg    0.10 0.8   0.12  1.1   0.14 1.8   0.18 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbonyl</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/carbonyl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/fishing/spools/carbonyl/</guid>
      <description>This fishing line is coated with fluorocarbon. Its main benefits are that it does not absorb water and its performance is not reduced inside the water.
The nylon that it contains, ensures excellent tensile strength and resistance that surpass those of pure fluorocarbon.
Available packages:
 Spools from 100 to 300m. Hanks from 300 to 1000m.  100 m spool.  Round spool in blister package.  Package of hanks 300 - 1000 m.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>