<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TEXTILE on TECHMONFIL</title>
    <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TEXTILE on TECHMONFIL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PET-POLYESTER</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pet-polyester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pet-polyester/</guid>
      <description>PET monofilament is primarily used for the purposes of textile market.
The main fields of application are the production of curtain tapes, conveyor belts, tensile and binding belts, zips for clothing industry and filters for the paper industry.
Due to the nature of the raw material (its high melting point) and the formulation procedure it is subjected to, this type of monofilament presents great resistance against high temperatures and abrasion. This characteristic is easily recognised by the amount of resistance this monofilament presents against deformability and by its good reaction to chemical agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PA-POLYAMIDE</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pa-polyamide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pa-polyamide/</guid>
      <description>This monofilament is purposed to be used as a sewing thread. Its basic raw material is polyamide.
In order to serve the needs of the textile industry we have developed a PA monofilament line which is transparent and doesn’t shrink when exposed to high temperatures. It also demonstrates high tensile strength, abrasion and and a great diameter uniformity.
It can be used to sew any type of garment either for industrial or amateur purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PE-PΟLYETHYLENE</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pe-polyethylene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pe-polyethylene/</guid>
      <description>Raw Material: High Density Polyethylene (HDPE).
Fields of application: Production of mosquito nets, nets for the food industry, nets for the agricultural industry such as nets for the collection of olives, tow ropes, tapes for the furniture industry, special nets for sports camps. PE can also be used as a contributory factor in certain paper or plastic products.
Colours: Light green, dark green, red, white and any other colour by order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PP-POLYPROPELENE</title>
      <link>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pp-polypropylene/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techmonfil.github.io/en/products/textile/pp-polypropylene/</guid>
      <description>Raw material: Polypropylene
Fields of application: Curtain tapes, filters and more.
Resistant to acids and other chemical derivatives.
Colours: Transparent, white and any other colour by order.
Diameters: 0.18 - 0.35 mm</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>